import nanoid from "nanoid";

const START_DECKS = [
  {
    id: nanoid(),
    name: "CSS",
    cards: [
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "Mexico",
        answer: "Mexico City",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "Saudi Arabia",
        answer: "Riyadh",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "Germany",
        answer: "Berlin",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "United Kingdom",
        answer: "London",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "China PR",
        answer: "Beijing",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "Egypt",
        answer: "Cairo",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "Japan",
        answer: "Tokyo",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "Russia",
        answer: "Moscow",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "South Korea",
        answer: "Seoul",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "India",
        answer: "New Delhi",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "Brasil",
        answer: "Brasilia",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "Italy",
        answer: "Rome",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "Argentina",
        answer: "Buenos Aires",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "New Zealand",
        answer: "Wellington",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "Colombia",
        answer: "Bofot√°",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "United States",
        answer: "Washington, D.C.",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "Canada",
        answer: "Ottawa",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "France",
        answer: "Paris",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "Australia",
        answer: "Canberra",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "Iran",
        answer: "Tehran",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "Peru",
        answer: "Lima",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "Iraq",
        answer: "Baghdad",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "DR Congo",
        answer: "Kinshasa",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "Algeria",
        answer: "Algiers",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "Chile",
        answer: "Santiago",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "Kenya",
        answer: "Nairobi",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "Ethiopia",
        answer: "Addis Ababa",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "Hong Kong",
        answer: "Hong Kong",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "Spain",
        answer: "Madrid",
        nailed: false,
      },
      {
        id: nanoid(),
        question: "South Africa",
        answer: "Pretoria",
        nailed: false,
      },
    ],
  },
];

export default START_DECKS;
